Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[The Tower of Whispers]
[برج الهمسات]
[Episode 11]
[الحلقة 11]
My dear.
عزيزي.
Yingying
ينغ ينغ
is over 18, right?
عمرك أكثر من 18 عامًا، أليس كذلك؟
She's already 20. She is no longer a child.
إنها في العشرين من عمرها بالفعل. لم تعد طفلة.
[Marriage Profile]
[ملف الزواج]
Shouldn't we start arranging
ألا ينبغي لنا أن نبدأ في الترتيب؟
Yingying's marriage?
زواج ينغ ينغ؟
Yes.
نعم.
[Marriage Profile]
[ملف الزواج]
Father, Mother, what's up?
أبي، أمي، ماذا يحدث؟
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
It occurs to me that
يخطر ببالي أن
from now on, my brother will be living at the Longxiang Guard Command Center.
من الآن فصاعدا، سوف يعيش أخي في مركز قيادة الحرس لونغشيانغ.
Take a look at these first.
ألقي نظرة على هذه أولاً.
Marriage profiles?
ملفات الزواج؟
These are the marriage profiles of
هذه هي ملفات تعريف الزواج الخاصة بـ
those talented and successful young men
هؤلاء الشباب الموهوبين والناجحين
around your age in the capital.
في عمرك تقريبًا في العاصمة.
Take your pick.
إختر ما يناسبك.
If you find someone suitable,
إذا وجدت شخصًا مناسبًا،
I'll send someone to arrange the match.
سأرسل شخصًا لترتيب المباراة.
No.
لا.
I just want to stay with you two forever.
أريد فقط أن أبقى معكما إلى الأبد.
Well...
حسنًا...
Silly child.
طفل سخيف.
People who come of age should get married.
ينبغي على الأشخاص الذين بلغوا سن الرشد أن يتزوجوا.
How could you stay with us forever?
كيف يمكنك البقاء معنا إلى الأبد؟
Just take a look first.
فقط قم بإلقاء نظرة أولاً.
Forget it if you don't want to marry someone.
انسي الأمر إذا كنت لا تريد الزواج من شخص ما.
However,
لكن،
your monthly allowance
مخصصاتك الشهرية
will be cut in half.
سيتم قطعها إلى النصف.
You always threaten me with that.
أنت تهددني دائما بهذا.
Yingying, be good and listen to us.
ينغ ينغ، كوني جيدة واستمعي إلينا.
Take these and have a look.
خذ هذه وألقي نظرة عليها.
Go back, read these profiles
ارجع واقرأ هذه الملفات الشخصية
and pick someone carefully.
وأختار شخصًا بعناية.
Take a good look.
خذ نظرة جيدة.
You really want to choose someone, huh?
هل تريد حقًا اختيار شخص ما، أليس كذلك؟
I had no choice.
لم يكن لدي خيار.
My parents insisted that I choose someone
أصر والدي على أن أختار شخصًا ما
or they would reduce my allowance.
أو أنهم سوف يقللون من مصروفي.
If you don't want to do it,
إذا كنت لا تريد أن تفعل ذلك،
it's easy to solve this problem.
من السهل حل هذه المشكلة.
What?
ماذا؟
You want to meet them?
هل تريد مقابلتهم؟
Don't tear them up! Give them back!
لا تمزقهم! أعدهم!
You want to keep them?
هل تريد الاحتفاظ بهم؟
They can't be torn.
لا يمكن تمزيقهم.
We can't!
نحن لا نستطيع!
These marriage profiles were carefully
تم إعداد ملفات تعريف الزواج هذه بعناية
selected by my parents.
تم اختياري من قبل والدي.
How could we tear them up?
كيف يمكننا تمزيقهم؟
I...
أنا...
I just accidentally
لقد فعلت ذلك بالصدفة
threw them all into the fire and burned them.
ألقاهم جميعا في النار وأحرقهم.
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
I accidentally threw
لقد رميت بالخطأ
all those marriage profiles into the fire.
كل تلك الملفات الشخصية للزواج في النار.
I tried to retrieve them
لقد حاولت استرجاعهم
but only got my hand burned.
ولكن فقط احترقت يدي.
You...
أنت...
Just as I expected.
كما توقعت.
Today,
اليوم،
I've invited all those talented young men
لقد دعوت كل هؤلاء الشباب الموهوبين
to come over.
لتأتي.
You can meet each of them
يمكنك مقابلة كل واحد منهم
to get to know them all.
للتعرف عليهم جميعا.
It is more direct than just reading their profiles.
إنه أكثر مباشرة من مجرد قراءة ملفاتهم الشخصية.
That's a bit too direct.
هذا مباشر بعض الشيء.
It's not convenient to
إنه ليس من الملائم
have so many people at our house.
لدينا الكثير من الناس في منزلنا.
You...
أنت...
I have foresight, don't I?
لدي نظرة ثاقبة، أليس كذلك؟
With this large screen here,
مع هذه الشاشة الكبيرة هنا،
you can hear their voices
يمكنك سماع أصواتهم
and see their silhouettes.
وانظر إلى صورهم الظلية.
But it's not a formal meeting.
ولكنه ليس اجتماعا رسميا.
You can talk about
يمكنك التحدث عن
whatever you want.
أياً كان ما تريد.
You're in such a hurry to marry me off?
أنت في عجلة من أمرك لتزويجني؟
You've gone to great lengths.
لقد قطعت شوطا كبيرا.
Alright, Yingying. Be good.
حسناً يا ينغ ينغ، كوني بخير.
Hurry up and go.
اسرع واذهب.
Your father and I are free today.
أنا وأبوك أحرار اليوم.
So, we'll go out for tea.
حسنًا، سنخرج لتناول الشاي.
Have a chat with them.
تحدث معهم.
My Lady, what should we do?
سيدتي ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Do not talk with them.
لا تتحدث معهم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Wait.
انتظر.
It's better to solve it once rather than keep avoiding it.
من الأفضل حل المشكلة مرة واحدة بدلاً من الاستمرار في تجنبها.
Don't my parents want me to talk with them?
هل لا يريد والدي أن أتحدث معهم؟
Then I'll speak freely
ثم سأتحدث بحرية
and say everything that we women
ونقول كل ما نقوله نحن النساء
want to say.
أريد أن أقول.
I assume all of you
أفترض أنكم جميعا
know something about my situation.
أعرف شيئا عن حالتي.
So let me tell you my criteria for choosing a husband.
دعوني أخبركم بمعاييري لاختيار الزوج.
If you want to marry me,
إذا كنت تريد الزواج مني،
we should live in harmony,
ينبغي لنا أن نعيش في وئام،
be understanding of each other, and communicate on an equal footing.
أن يكونوا متفهمين لبعضهم البعض، ويتواصلون على قدم المساواة.
It's easy.
إنه سهل.
Go on.
إستمر.
Since we're equals,
بما أننا متساوون،
we should discuss matters together,
ينبغي لنا أن نناقش الأمور معًا،
make decisions together,
اتخاذ القرارات معًا،
and share household chores.
وتقاسم الأعمال المنزلية.
It is too easy.
إنه سهل للغاية.
Is she in a hurry to get married?
هل هي مستعجلة على الزواج؟
Ridiculous!
سخيف!
Doing housework?
هل تقومين بالأعمال المنزلية؟
Don't you know that gentlemen should stay away from the kitchen?
ألا تعلم أن الرجال يجب أن يبتعدوا عن المطبخ؟
Do you want your husband to do dirty work, Miss Lu?
هل تريدين أن يقوم زوجك بأعمال قذرة يا آنسة لو؟
Since you've read the classics,
بما أنك قرأت الكلاسيكيات،
you should know that if one cannot clean his own house,
يجب أن تعلم أنه إذا لم يتمكن الإنسان من تنظيف منزله بنفسه،
he can't help govern the country.
فهو لا يستطيع المساعدة في حكم البلاد.
You...
أنت...
I am not destined to be with Miss Lu.
أنا لست مقدرًا أن أكون مع الآنسة لو.
I'll take my leave now.
سوف آخذ إجازتي الآن.
Mr. Zhou, since you came here by carriage,
السيد تشو، بما أنك أتيت إلى هنا بالعربة،
could you give me a ride?
هل يمكن أن توصلني إلى وجهتي؟
Let's go. Let's go.
دعنا نذهب. دعنا نذهب.
Okay. Okay.
حسناً. حسناً.
Then I'll continue.
ثم سأستمر.
My husband can't have any concubines in his life.
زوجي لا يستطيع أن يكون له أي محظيات في حياته.
The first child born
الطفل الأول المولود
must take my surname.
يجب أن يأخذ لقبي.
Not taking concubines is already too much,
إن عدم اتخاذ محظيات هو بالفعل أمر مبالغ فيه،
and now the child must take her surname?
والآن يجب على الطفلة أن تأخذ لقبها؟
There has never been such a rule throughout history.
لم تكن هناك مثل هذه القاعدة عبر التاريخ.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
-There has never been such a rule! -Miss Lu is too domineering!
-لم تكن هناك مثل هذه القاعدة أبدًا! -الآنسة لو مسيطرة جدًا!
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
I haven't finished yet.
لم أنتهي بعد.
This last item is that
هذا العنصر الأخير هو
my husband can't keep me stuck at home
لا يستطيع زوجي أن يبقيني حبيسة المنزل
in the name of love.
باسم الحب.
I have ambitions just like men.
لدي طموحات مثل الرجال تمامًا.
My husband must not restrict my freedom.
لا ينبغي لزوجي أن يقيد حريتي.
Miss Lu has such high demands.
لدى السيدة لو مطالب عالية جدًا.
I would like to see
أود رؤية
how beautiful you are.
كم انت جميلة.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Indeed, you are a beauty.
أنت جميلة بالفعل.
Miss Lu, your features resemble someone.
آنسة لو، ملامحك تشبه شخصًا ما.
I remember now.
انا أتذكر الآن.
You look like Honglian of the Diecui Brothel.
أنت تبدو مثل هونغليان من بيت الدعارة دييكوي.
She is the newly crowned courtesan.
إنها العاهرة المتوجة حديثًا.
It is said that it would only cost a maximum of 100 taels of silver
ويقال أن التكلفة القصوى ستكون 100 تايل من الفضة فقط
to spend a night with her.
لقضاء ليلة معها.
Sir, you needn't compare me with a courtesan
سيدي، لا داعي لمقارنتي مع العاهرة
to insult me.
لإهانتي.
Because I don't care.
لأنني لا أهتم.
What's wrong with being a courtesan?
ما هو الخطأ في أن تكون مومسًا؟
If this is your understanding,
إذا كان هذا هو فهمك،
why bother coming here?
لماذا تأتي إلى هنا؟
You just don't know how to be a good wife.
أنت لا تعرفين كيف تكونين زوجة جيدة.
How dare you make such demands of men!
كيف تجرؤ على مطالبة الرجال بمثل هذه المطالب!
Yes. Exactly!
نعم، بالضبط!
Ridiculous!
سخيف!
I'm merely asking for
انا فقط اسأل عن
loyalty and respect from my future husband.
الولاء والاحترام من زوجي المستقبلي.
But you think I'm being improper.
لكنك تعتقد أنني غير لائق.
What about all those demands
ماذا عن كل تلك المطالب؟
you put forward to the matchmaker?
هل تقدمت إلى الخاطبة؟
Can I say you're failing to uphold male virtue?
هل يمكنني أن أقول أنك فشلت في الحفاظ على الفضيلة الذكورية؟
You...
أنت...
All I want is
كل ما أريده هو
monogamy.
الزواج الأحادي.
Is that difficult?
هل هذا صعب؟
Wishful thinking.
تفكير متفائل.
Who dares hit me?
من يجرؤ على ضربي؟
I think it was karma.
أعتقد أنها كانت الكارما.
I'd better not get involved with her.
من الأفضل أن لا أتدخل معها.
Let's go. Let's go.
دعنا نذهب. دعنا نذهب.
Let's get out of here.
دعونا نخرج من هنا.
That's great, My Lady.
هذا رائع، سيدتي.
They all left.
لقد غادروا جميعا.
What an impressive woman!
يا لها من امرأة مثيرة للإعجاب!
I'm still here.
أنا لا أزال هنا.
This way, Young Master.
من هنا يا سيدي الشاب.
I think all of Miss Lu's demands
أعتقد أن جميع مطالب الآنسة لو
can be fulfilled.
يمكن تحقيقها.
It's you.
إنه أنت.
Yingying,
ينغ ينغ،
long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Hong'an.
هونغآن.
I remember you were chubby when you were young.
أتذكر أنك كنت ممتلئ الجسم عندما كنت صغيرا.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I was often bullied because I was fat.
لقد تعرضت للتنمر في كثير من الأحيان لأنني كنت سمينة.
You were the only one who played with me.
لقد كنت الشخص الوحيد الذي لعب معي.
Do you remember that
هل تتذكر ذلك؟
we used to catch butterflies together.
كنا نصطاد الفراشات معًا.
Yes. I loved butterflies.
نعم، لقد أحببت الفراشات.
So we always tried to catch butterflies together.
لذلك كنا نحاول دائمًا أن نلتقط الفراشات معًا.
But we were too clumsy.
لكننا كنا أخرقين للغاية.
We never managed to catch one.
لم نتمكن من اصطياد واحدة أبدًا.
So this time,
لذا هذه المرة،
I brought a butterfly especially for you.
لقد أحضرت لك فراشة خصيصًا.
No, this is too valuable.
لا، هذا ثمين للغاية.
I can't accept it.
لا أستطيع قبول ذلك.
We're close. So, do not talk about the value of it.
نحن قريبون، لذا لا تتحدث عن قيمته.
A bracelet is an intimate item.
السوار هو عنصر حميم.
You're just an outsider.
أنت مجرد شخص غريب.
How can you give her a bracelet casually?
كيف يمكنك أن تعطيها سوارًا بشكل عرضي؟
Who is this gentleman?
من هو هذا الرجل؟
I'm her bodyguard.
أنا حارسها الشخصي.
He's Five.
إنه في الخامسة من عمره.
I'm also called Five.
أنا أيضا أُدعى بالخمسة.
How could a decent guy be called Five.
كيف يمكن لرجل محترم أن يُطلق عليه اسم "خمسة"؟
Isn't it a servant's name?
أليس هذا اسم خادم؟
Five.
خمسة.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
I can't accept this bracelet.
لا أستطيع قبول هذا السوار.
Please don't feel pressured.
من فضلك لا تشعر بالضغط.
This is just a small gift
هذه مجرد هدية صغيرة
I'm giving you as a friend.
انا أعطيك كصديق.
Besides, if I'm going to give you something,
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، إذا كنت سأعطيك شيئا،
how could I possibly just give you a butterfly?
كيف يمكنني أن أعطيك فراشة؟
Five.
خمسة.
Coming, Young Master.
قادم يا سيدي الشاب.
Young Master has prepared
لقد أعد السيد الشاب
a golden butterfly
فراشة ذهبية
for everyone in Lu's Mansion.
للجميع في قصر لو.
Well...
حسنًا...
It will cost you too much.
سوف يكلفك الكثير.
These are just....
هذه فقط....
Our Young Master is rich.
سيدنا الشاب غني.
He is the wealthiest man in the capital.
إنه أغنى رجل في العاصمة.
You're too talkative.
أنت ثرثارة للغاية.
I'll slap myself.
سأصفع نفسي.
Stop. Stop.
توقف. توقف.
Stop.
قف.
Give them away now.
تبرع بهم الآن.
Well,
حسنًا،
one for each person.
واحدة لكل شخص.
Soon, everyone in Lu's Mansion
قريبا، الجميع في قصر لو
will have a butterfly.
سيكون لدي فراشة.
Yingying will be happy to see that.
سوف تكون ينغ ينغ سعيدة برؤية ذلك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
thank you, Hong'an.
شكرا لك، هونغآن.
I'll visit you another day
سأزورك في يوم آخر
with gifts.
مع الهدايا.
Yingying, no need to be so polite.
ينغ ينغ، لا داعي لأن تكوني مهذبة جدًا.
Yingying, can you help me up?
ينغ ينغ، هل يمكنك مساعدتي على النهوض؟
You have leg pain, right?
هل تعاني من آلام في ساقك؟
Do you need me to set your bone?
هل تحتاجني لأضع عظمك؟
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
You scared him.
لقد اخافته.
This gentleman is feeling unwell.
هذا الرجل يشعر بتوعك.
He should seek medical attention now.
ينبغي عليه طلب العناية الطبية الآن.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I've arranged a dinner party.
لقد قمت بترتيب حفل عشاء.
What about checking on my leg after we have dinner?
ماذا عن التحقق من ساقي بعد تناول العشاء؟
Okay.
تمام.